JANICE LIN

UI/UX Designer

anicelin852.github.io/JaniceLin

janicelin852@gmail.com

+886-978-930887

UI/UX designer with background in design, research and education. As a designer, I enjoy solving complex problems through the design process and continuing to improve my abilities by joining book clubs and keeping up with design trends. I'm in a positive frame of mind and always look on the bright side of things.

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer

Jun 2021 - Now

ORing Industrial Networking Corp.

- Define and design a B2B SaaS platform to integrate the company's previously projects, reduce internal staff learning load, and improve data usability.
- Build, redefine and maintain Web and App design systems to shorten the development time, enhance product identity and maintain consistency.
- Understand the use case and conduct competitive analysis and design modifications based on project requirements.

Information Specialist

Aug 2019 - May 2021

National Center for Suicide Prevention

- Manage a digital learning site for 10,000+ healthcare professionals.
- Assist users in resolving website issues. To significantly lower the call rate, redesign the website's architecture and expand the email support system.
- Graphic design, event photography, video filming.

EDUCATION

M.S. in Digital Learning and Education

National Taiwan University of Science and Technology

Taiwan, Taipei | Sep 2017 - Jul 2019

B.A. in Digital content and techlonogy

National Taichung University of Education

Taiwan, Taichung | Sep 2012 - Jun 2016

CERTIFICATIONS

Google UX Design certificate unofficial public welfare book club

Volunteer

Introduction to Human-Centered Design

IDEO.org

SKILLS

Wireframing
Prototyping
Usertesting
User interface design
Visual design

TOOLS

Figma/Sketch Adobe Creative Suite HTML/CSS

LANGUAGE

English Mandarin Chinese

林家鈴

UI/UX Designer

anicelin852.github.io/JaniceLin

janicelin852@gmail.com +886-978-930887

我是一個有設計、研究及教育背景的設計師,對於介面設計與使用者體驗設計充滿熱情。作為一個設計師,喜歡透過設計流程來解決複雜的問題,並藉由參加讀書會與關注設計趨勢來不斷提升能力。我樂觀且積極,總是把事情往好的方向想。



經歷

UI/UX Designer

2021.6 - 現在

威力工業網絡股份有限公司

- · 定義與設計 B2B SaaS 平台,整合公司過去分散的專案,降低內部人員學習負荷,提升資料使用性
- ·建立、重新定義及維護 Web 與 App 設計系統,加速開發時間、提升公司產品識別及維持形象一致性
- · 根據專案需求,了解使用情境,進行競品分析與設計修改
- ·與PM、軟體工程師、韌體工程師跨部門合作融洽

資訊專員

2019.8 - 2021.5

社團法人台灣自殺防治學會

- · 管理一萬人以上的專業醫護人員學習平台
- · 客服協助使用者解決在平台上遇到的問題,重新規劃網站架構及增加 email 協助管道,有效降低來電率
- · 平面設計、活動攝影、影片剪輯

教育

數位學習與教育研究所

國立臺灣科技大學

臺灣,臺北 2017.9 - 2019.7

數位內容科技學系

國立臺中教育大學

臺灣,臺中 2012.9 - 2016.6

證照

Google UX Design certificate 非官方公益讀書

志工

Introduction to Human-Centered Design IDEO.org

技能

Wireframing
Prototyping
Usertesting
User interface design
Visual design

工具

Figma/Sketch Adobe Creative Suite HTML/CSS

語言

英文 中文